<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Real Estate Systems Integrator</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>RESI was established in 1994 with the purpose of providing REALTORS® with the technology necessary to enhance productivity and broaden their reach. The main office of the company is located at: 560 Lincoln Rd Ste 203, Miami Beach, Florida, 33139, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?9adf5dc5-1371-11ee-b4cf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Universitas Matthiae Belii association</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Matej Bel University (commonly referred as Matej Bel or UMB), (Slovak: Univerzita Mateja Bela) is a public research university in the central Slovak town of Banská Bystrica. The university was established in 1992. At the moment, more than 6,000 students are studying at the university.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?9adf7dca-1371-11ee-8e01-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 13:17:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomexx has just published a now post : Jacobs Farm</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx</link><description>Jacobs Farm was founded in 1980 as a small organic family farm dedicated to growing fresh, high quality, delicious food without damaging the environment.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx?9adf803a-1371-11ee-a4e5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 20:50:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : The City of Nassau Bay</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>The City of Nassau Bay is an incomparable community at the leading edge of technology. But being on the edge is dangerous sometimes. As the city government says theydon't have evidences that the personal information hasbeen compromised. We are willing to provide some evidence of personal files in 45GB data we have for them to be sure. We have made the process of uploading company data as simple as possible for our users. All you need is any torrent client (like Vuze, Utorrent, qBittorrent or Transmission to use magnet links). You will find the torrentfile above.1. Open uTorrent, or any another torrent client.2. Add torrent file or paste the magnet URL to upload the data safely.3. Archives have no password.MAGNET URL: magnet:?xt=urn:btih</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adf82c1-1371-11ee-919c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Tlantic</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>INFO: https://www.zoominfo.com/c/tlantic/346591091  DATA: https://anonfiles.com/h6F8rcybz7/tlantic_7z PASSWORD: 77UXD&amp;CNqq@c+2rX$46~Y895rQX7Th7j </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?9adf845d-1371-11ee-9401-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 06:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusalocker has just published a now post : reutlingen.ihk.de</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker</link><description>DescriptionClient Case – agreement – email(.msg)- contracts – and other documents PRICE-$80000</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker?9adf864c-1371-11ee-830d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusalocker has just published a now post : Hausamman company</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker</link><description>DescriptionClient Case – customers email-documents PRICE-$20000</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker?9adf87ae-1371-11ee-ae89-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 23:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusalocker has just published a now post : kafflogistic.hu</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker</link><description>DescriptionClient Case – agreement – email(outlook files)- contracts – and other documents PRICE-$50000</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker?9adf88dc-1371-11ee-b4c9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusalocker has just published a now post : SELL DATA(qtox)</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker</link><description>Available for sale: to buy please contact qtox price negotiable qtox-E9CD65687463F67F64937E961DD723DC82C79CB548375AAE8AA4A0698D356C5E7E157B22E8CD</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusalocker?9adf8a15-1371-11ee-bd40-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : MSAMLIN.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>MS Amlin - Global Specialty Insurer and Reinsurer</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?9adf8b3a-1371-11ee-a3dc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 22:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ noescape has just published a now post : Credit Team</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/noescape</link><description>Provider of subsidized finance and credit brokerage intended to increase liquidity and company growth. The company's services include obtaining non-repayable grants, tax bonuses and subsidized loans for micro SMEs, start...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/noescape?9adf8cce-1371-11ee-ab55-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : **** H****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Company is one of the oldest and most storied names in the musical products industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?9adf8dee-1371-11ee-a76d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : *i***** *****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Company is a global business conglomerate with a diverse interest in Pharma, Financial Services, Healthcare Information Management, etc..</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?9adf8f55-1371-11ee-b998-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:53:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : American Crane Rental</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Company operates in truck &amp; crane rental Industry, 15 ton to 350 ton hydraulic cranes bare boom truck rental, standard mount to swing cabs machinery relocation, and other transportation vehicles.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?9adf9083-1371-11ee-b9ef-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : The Akron-Summit County Public Library</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>The Akron-Summit County Public Library is an organization dedicated to providing reading, learning and other opportunities and programs for members of the community. Soon there will be another opportunity for customers of this library and others who are interested: you will be able to review any staff document for free. Keep in mind that your documents may be there, too. This informationand the rest of the internal library will be available here shortly.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adf91a0-1371-11ee-8ac2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Perpetual Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>Perpetual Group is a diversified financial services company whichhas been serving Australians since 1886 when it was established as a trustee company by a group of businessmen. The information about the Australian this group served will soon be available in our blog for everyone. 700GB of databases with highly detailed business information in total.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adf92b9-1371-11ee-9504-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Galveston College</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>Galveston College provides residents of Galveston Island and the surrounding region with academic, workforce development, continuing education and community service programs. We decided to check and show you if you can protect yourself from cyber attacks on the island and realized you can't. Soon you'll see the results of our work with this client here. Much student detailed personal info. 99GB.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adf93d3-1371-11ee-a774-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : GUSCANADA.CA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?9adf9557-1371-11ee-ba6a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : PWC.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>PwC: Building trust for today and tomorrow</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?9adf966a-1371-11ee-a133-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : EY.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>EY US - Home -  Building a better working world</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?9adf9797-1371-11ee-8abb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : SONY.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Sony Group Portal - Home</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?9adf98ba-1371-11ee-884d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : ANDESASERVICES.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Policy Lifecycle Solutions Provider for Life Insurance &amp; Annuities Industry - Andesa</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?9adf99e9-1371-11ee-b069-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : M&amp;M Industries</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>M&amp;M Industries, Inc. is a US-based plastic pail manufacturer which was established in 1986 by Glenn Morris, Sr. Mr. Morris began in 1963 packaging over-the-counter remedies. An inventor who has 44 patents for his ingenious ideas, he saw the need for a “child-resistant” cap to assure safety for prescription products, and developed one. Today the company is owned and operated by his son, Glenn Morris. M&amp;M Industries has two manufacturing plants in Chattanooga, TN in addition to plants in Phoenix, AZ and Lordstown, OH. We have the capability to print using dry offset printing, in-mould labeling or heat transfer labeling. M&amp;M employs individuals committed to excellence and quality. We believe in customer service and personal attention. M&amp;M Industries is a manufacturer of containers for hazardous and non-hazardous solids and liquids. The containers we manufacture are ideal for biohazard waste, hazardous chemicals, solid waste and solid chemicals. Most containers are U.N. Certified and are made with FDA grade materials.SITE: https://www.ultimatepail.com Address  316 CORPORATE PLACE CHATTANOOGA, TN 37419</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?9adf9b89-1371-11ee-88e8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 08:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ qilin has just published a now post : Daiwa House Industry Co.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin</link><description>Daiwa House Industry Co., Ltd. is Japan's largest homebuilder, specializing in prefabricated houses. The company is also engaged in the construction of factories, shopping centers, health care facilities, the management and operation of resor            ...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin?9adf9ca7-1371-11ee-9f38-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 22:02:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Hill International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Pennsylvania, USA</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adf9dc4-1371-11ee-832b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 22:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : National Institutional Facilitation Technologies (Pvt.) Limited</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>National Institutional Facilitation Technologies (Pvt.) Limited. NIFT is the only Automated Cheque Clearing House and the prominent Payment System Operator in Pakistan.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?9adf9ee4-1371-11ee-8f36-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 17:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Refractron</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>Refractron has created resilient, innovative ceramic-based solutions since 1984, offering responsive customer service and accountability to maintain each client relationship with the best care possible. Their cyber security systems are not so resilient and innovative and that unfortunate fact caused their data will be uploaded to our blog these days.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adfa074-1371-11ee-ae02-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : DBSA hit by ransomware attack.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>The Bank was attacked using Akira ransomware by an unknown actor without any permissions or approves from our side.We are ready to provide any assistance needed to help DBSA recover it's systems and would like to ask their representative to contact us anytime.We are currently conducting an internal investigation to ensure that DBSA information is not leaked. A bank representative will beprovided with all the details of the incident.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adfa1c3-1371-11ee-a5da-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : GC&amp;E</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>GC&amp;E provides Information Technology (IT), security, and telecommunications solutions. GC&amp;E also provides consultation, design, and implementation. Markets served are federal, state and local, K-12 and higher education, healthcare and commercial markets. We are going to show you how this company looks inside soon. Think twice before consulting with these professionals about cyber security.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adfa2f1-1371-11ee-99da-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : londonandcapital</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>PRIVATE WEALTH MANAGEMENT We work with HNW and UHNW individuals to provide an integrated wealth management solution which includes financial planning, tailored investment management and multi-currency reporting.  With offices in London and Barcelona, and a dedicated team who specialise in ex-pat Americans, we are perfectly positioned to provide a truly borderless wealth management solution.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?9adfa418-1371-11ee-84ee-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 11:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ rhysida has just published a now post : Avannubo</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/rhysida</link><description>Avannubo Global provider of technological services with an official license for IP telephony, mobile phones and Internet access.  Documents Data Catalog: 165Gb, 198760 Files  100%   																					All files was uploaded to public access, data hunters, enjoy 																			  More</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/rhysida?9adfa53b-1371-11ee-b1fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 21:03:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : CYBERFREIGHT SYSTEMS MARITIMES INC.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>Cyberfreight Maritimes Inc., is a Canadian transportation and logistics management company. We have over 100 years of transportation knowledge and a worldwide network of offices.To provide the most reliable, expeditious and economical means of transportation to exporters and importers without compromise, thus participating in their growth.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?9adfa65f-1371-11ee-a014-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Craig &amp; Associates, LLC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Craig &amp;amp; Associates, LLC was incorporated August 1, 1980.  We have been serving individuals and businesses for over 40 years and offer a variety of services: income tax preparation, strategic tax planning, financial planning, estate planning, retirement planning, insurance planning, investment review, auditing &amp;amp; accounting services, recordkeeping &amp;amp; reports, payroll &amp;amp; sales tax services, pension &amp;amp; profit sharing plan services and incorporations &amp;amp; partnerships. We work with several types of businesses including Corporations, S-Corporations, Partnerships, Condominium Associations, Municipalities and Not-for-Profit Organizations.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?9adfa7a8-1371-11ee-a3eb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Main Street Title and Settlement Services LLC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>MAIN STREET TITLE BEGAN IN 1988 WITH DOMINICK DECARLO AND 3 EMPLOYEES ON MAIN STREET IN HACKENSACK. Rates were high and searches were done manually at the courthouse. Every file was handled with care and individual attention to detail to ensure a smooth closing.  As the years progressed, our client base grew as well as our team. Processes were streamlined and our services expanded to include settlement, thus creating Main Street Title and Settlement in 2007.  With over 50 employees and growing, Main Street Title and Settlement has become one of the leading title insurance and settlement agencies in the New Jersey / New York Tristate Area. We continue to expand our service offerings and tools to be the best partners to our clients, near and far.  The Team at Main Street prides itself on service, integrity, education and innovation, stemming from the foundation Mr. DeCarlo set forth since the beginning. Today, our Executive Team continues to lead the agency in providing quality customer service to each and every client. In addition, they play an active role within the community, including involvement in fund-raisers for many local and regional charitable organizations.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?9adfa8dd-1371-11ee-8df4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Habasit</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>Habasit is a manufacturer of timing and conveyor belts, includingfabric-based belts, plastic modular belts, and power transmission belts. They service the food, textile, wood, paper, postal, materials handling. Soon they will serve any interested individual in our blog conveying their corporate data to our blog. We hope their conveyors are strong enough for files of 470GB size.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adfaa90-1371-11ee-bc98-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Café Soluble</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>Café Soluble is a Nicaraguan privately held company. They produceand market powdered nutritional beverages, cereals, soy-based products, roasted and ground coffee. This company has a modern distribution chain of products and is ready to distribute it's 330 GBof corporate data to our blog. Btw, they work with Nestle. So you can find something really interesting in their fails.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adfabfa-1371-11ee-b493-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Peter Mark</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Leinster, Ireland</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfada8-1371-11ee-a97f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Dancie Perugini Ware Public Relations</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Texas, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfaf38-1371-11ee-87ab-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:55:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Summit Hut</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Arizona, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfb0b3-1371-11ee-9a97-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Kansas Joint &amp; Spine Specialists</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Founded in 1976, Kansas Joint &amp;amp; Spine Specialists, formerly Orthopaedic &amp;amp; Sports Medicine at Cypress, has been committed to delivering the exceptional bone, joint, and muscle care patients need to make today theirs. Our orthopaedic surgeons, doctors, and medical staff are dedicated to improving the lives of residents in Wichita, Scott City, El Dorado, Anthony, and the surrounding areas in Kansas as well as treating each patient with courtesy, respect, and compassion.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?9adfb1c0-1371-11ee-8c24-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Yokohama-oht (atgtire)</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>Yokohama Off-Highway Tires America Inc is a company that operatesin the Automotive industry. A well-known name in tire business is going to share it's secrets in our blog. The data we took from them is of 1.3TB size will be available for you soon.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?9adfb2d0-1371-11ee-a9ae-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : OMNIPOL</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Czech Republic</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfb41e-1371-11ee-b335-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Hi-tec, Batra Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfb53d-1371-11ee-a220-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Barentz North America</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Ohio, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfb6e5-1371-11ee-aa06-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : PWI Engineering</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>New Jersey, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfb829-1371-11ee-abc4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Federation Francaise de Rugby</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>France</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfb946-1371-11ee-b021-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Luís Simoes</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Portugal</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfba5a-1371-11ee-ac30-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Allpro Consulting Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Texas, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfbb96-1371-11ee-a04c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Lorclon</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?9adfbcc9-1371-11ee-9ebc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ karakurt has just published a now post : Eastside Union School District</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/karakurt</link><description>Eastside Union School District seeks to provide an inclusive, challenging and innovative education in a safe, positive and rigorous learning environment with dynamic and responsive staff. The size of files we've taken - 18Gb. Accounting, personal information and so on. Everything will be uploaded during upcoming release.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/karakurt?9adfbe09-1371-11ee-a4cd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>