<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : eyedoc.com.na</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Emoneko is a Namibian health and eye care company with a vision to improve the lives ofNamibians through superior service and care, combined with world-class technology.Established in 2018, Emoneko is the management company overseeing the activit...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?08d1856e-223f-11ee-9a21-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : CPA Advisors Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>Our accounting firm was formed with a single principle in mind: to provide the highest level of personalized client service possible. Simply put, we care about each and every one of our clients.  If you would like to develop a relationship with an accountant that will know your name, get to know ours.Our full-service accounting firm is well established and is ready to serve you. Since our inception, we have grown continuously by providing a wide-array of professional services. Let us know how we can serve you. We’re here to help.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1a47a-223f-11ee-af54-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : Info Salons</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>Many people will ask why we are called Info Salons? Does it have anything to do with haircuts? This is related to our CEO Ms. Jo-Anne Kelleway's work experience in a French exhibition registration management company. The word "salons" refers to exhibitions in French. So Info Salons literally means information technology applied to exhibitions.Info Salons was established in Australia in 1990. At that time, Australia's convention and exhibition industry began to boom with the opening of the new Sydney Convention and Exhibition Center on the edge of Darling Harbour. Australia needs a professional data collection company to professionalize the convention and exhibition industry. Info Salons provided registration solutions for 10 shows in its first year.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1a8cf-223f-11ee-8516-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ rhysida has just published a now post : The Big Life group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/rhysida</link><description>The Big Life group Big Life is in the business of changing lives. We fight inequality by working with people and places to create opportunities and inspire change.    More</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/rhysida?08d1ac28-223f-11ee-937e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:05:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Gerber ChildrenswearLLC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>Gerber Childrenswear LLC is a leading marketer of infant and toddler apparel and related products in the marketplace. Almost 0.5TBof data will be uploaded to our blog soon. So detailed business information is there: patents, trademarks, contracts with other business giants. Much to look through.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?08d1ade0-223f-11ee-9156-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : Blackjewel L.L.C.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>We give you a unique chance to see the corporation Blackjewel LLC from the inside. This is the third large US coal company so it will be interesting.To your attention more than 500gb of documents, databases, Accounting, Audit, data of all branches...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?08d1b0f2-223f-11ee-866d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : SHUTTERFLY.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Shutterfly: Photo Books, Cards, Prints, Wall Art, Gifts, Wedding</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1b355-223f-11ee-9556-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : DISCOVERY.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1b4d2-223f-11ee-8893-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : ASPENTECH.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>AspenTech - Asset Optimization Software - Asset Performance Management, Process Engineering for Chemicals, Energy and Engineering &amp; Construction</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1b618-223f-11ee-8750-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : MOTHERSON.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1b7ec-223f-11ee-a066-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : PAYCOM.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Online Payroll Services - HR Payroll Software - Paycom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1b971-223f-11ee-83e3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 12:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : Telepizza</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>Telepizza was founded in Madrid in 1987 as a family business with a clear drive for innovation and a constant focus on the quality of its products. Being in this way a pioneer in the delivery of quality food to home. In 1992, the company opened its first factory and began its international expansion.Telepizza's focus of work is occupied by irresistible and unique pizzas. Prepared with the utmost attention to detail and a rigorous selection of fresh and natural ingredients. His secret is known. Mass. Made with love and by hand.In addition, through Telepizza's communication platform, Let's spend more time together, we become a global brand with a unique meaning throughout the world.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1baa7-223f-11ee-aaa1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : The Traffic Tech</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>The Traffic Tech Gull is an award winning ISO certified total solutions provider of integrated systems in traffic management. intelligent transportation, parking management, security, communications and truck weigh stations. Founded in 2000, Traffic Tech Experience in Tratic Engineering, integrating systems to meet customized needs using the most advanced technologies available in the market, Over the past twenty (20) years, Taffic Tech has developed com engineering, system integration, contracting and service capabilities, that helped earn Trafic Tech a leading role in the balds of specialization throughout the Gulf regions. Our scope includes design, system integration equipment supply installation, commissioning, operation, and after-sales service.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1bd3c-223f-11ee-aa05-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : Quikcard Solutions Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>QSi has been providing consulting services for over 20 years. QSi has worked with a select group of clients who possess an ardent desire for growth and realize that the recruitment of key talent is critical. Our experience and specialization translates into a clearer understanding of client needs and a shortened recruitment cycle.With Quikcard, businesses can have a benefits plan that's flexible and offers dental, medical, vision, and group travel insurance. Quikcard has been supporting Canadian businesses for over 30 years.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1beaf-223f-11ee-a50d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : Jadranka Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>Since its founding, Jadranka has been the largest company on the islands of Cres and Lošinj. It also employs the largest number of inhabitants of these islands and is the main driver of the development of this area. Jadranka has grown into a recognizable and respected company with a 70-year-old business tradition, which, according to business results, can certainly be ranked among the top companies in the hospitality and tourism industry.During February 2014, Jadranka d.d. went through the process of ownership change and thus the company Beta ulaganja d.o.o. based in Zagreb became 100% owner of Jadranka's shares. Croatian owners of Beta ulaganja are officially recorded in the Register of Beneficial Owners.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1bfe8-223f-11ee-a8fe-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : Dental One Craigieburn</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>Dental One was created to make Dentistry more affordable and accessible in Australia, starting with our home state of Victoria.Cost has long been sighted as the number one reason people avoid visiting the dentist. At Dental One we aim to remove this obstacle and usher in a new wave of Affordable Dental Care for all. You can expect the same quality and professional treatment from our Dentists as you would anywhere else. We are focused on providing the best outcome for our patients and ensuring only the best long-term treatment options are followed. At Dental One we aim to usher in a new wave of Affordable Dental Care for all. We are focused on providing the best outcome for our patients and ensuring only the best long-term treatment options are followed.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1c144-223f-11ee-ac3f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : ANL Packaging</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>ANL Packaging makes your product uniqueANL Packaging specializes in bespoke thermoformed packaging in line with the customers’ needs. In doing so, ANL Packaging supports the individuality of the customers’ products.ANL Packaging specializes in bespoke thermoformed plastic packaging. Our custom-made packaging solutions can be found in both food and non-food markets, but we also have a standard range.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1c281-223f-11ee-939e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a now post : BTU</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base</link><description>BTU is an Argentine company dedicated to the development and execution of engineering, construction, mounting and start-up projects, mainly in the Energy, Oil &amp; Gas and Railway System Infrastructure sectors.We have provided integral services throughout the country for over 30 years, in public and private sector, delivering constant technical and entrepreneurial development. As a result of our expertise, we are one of Argentina’s leading engineering and highly complex construction company.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/8base?08d1c3df-223f-11ee-818d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ stormous has just published a now post : Ministerio de Cultura de la Republica de Cuba " STORMOUS + GhostSec "</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/stormous</link><description>Ministerio de Cultura de la Republica de Cuba - The triumph of the Cuban Revolution, government cultural functions were performed by the Department of Culture, Ministry of Education and the weight of cultural management lay with the management of private institutions and voluntary associations In 1961 the National Council for Culture was founded as the first independent government institution responsible for cultural policy development</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/stormous?08d1c51f-223f-11ee-9b6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 23:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ stormous has just published a now post : Ministry of Foreign Trade " STORMOUS + GhostSec "</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/stormous</link><description>It is the body of the Central State Administration in charge of proposing, and once approved, directing, executing and controlling State and Government policies in matters of foreign trade, foreign investment and international economic collaboration</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/stormous?08d1c65a-223f-11ee-942a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 23:10:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ stormous has just published a now post : Ministry of Energy and Mines (Cuba) " STORMOUS + GhostSec "</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/stormous</link><description>Ministry of Energy and Mines . Ministry created on December 3 , 2012 as an agreement of a meeting of the Council of Ministers of the Republic of Cuba [1] . It is the result of the transformation of the former Ministry of Basic Industry and its main objective is to respond to the problems identified in the sector of its competence - oil, electricity and mining - as well as to advance in the separation of state and business functions</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/stormous?08d1c7ec-223f-11ee-84e2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 23:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : GRIPA.ORG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Greater Rochester Independent Practice Association – GRIPA</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1c9f0-223f-11ee-a4ac-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : SLB.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>SLB, a global technology company - SLB</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1cb02-223f-11ee-82fc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : AMCTHEATRES.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>AMC Theatres - movie times, movie trailers, buy tickets and gift cards.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1cf6a-223f-11ee-b574-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : AINT.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>        Advanced Integration Technology    </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1d1d8-223f-11ee-9f4b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : JACKENTERTAINMENT.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>JACK Entertainment - Gaming, Hospitality &amp; Entertainment</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1d2fb-223f-11ee-b358-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : NASCO.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>NASCO – NASCO is a healthcare company dedicated to co-creating digital health solutions for Blue Cross and Blue Shield companies.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1d4b7-223f-11ee-8943-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : TGIDIRECT.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1d6fa-223f-11ee-846d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : HONEYWELL.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Honeywell - The Future Is What We Make It</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1d8bc-223f-11ee-8abf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : CLEARESULT.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>CLEAResult - Energy efficiency, transition and decarbonization solutions</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1dbb0-223f-11ee-a4ad-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : RADIUSGS.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Omnichannel Customer Experience Outsourcing - Radius</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1ddd7-223f-11ee-9230-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ arvinclub has just published a now post : Bitimen exchange</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/arvinclub</link><description>A harmful truth is better than a useful lie</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/arvinclub?08d1e021-223f-11ee-9265-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : affinityhealthservices.ne</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?08d1e2fc-223f-11ee-b907-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : ATS Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Indian real estate company.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?08d1e4fe-223f-11ee-aa98-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:02:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Henock Construction</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>A company that operates in the Construction industry. It employs 6-10 people and has $1M-$5M of revenue.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?08d1e648-223f-11ee-9be0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:02:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Lyon &amp; Healy</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Founded in 1864, Lyon &amp; Healy is one of the oldest and most storied names in the musical products industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?08d1e776-223f-11ee-a46d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Mission Parks</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>A company that operates in the Individual &amp; Family Services industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?08d1e89f-223f-11ee-abb8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 19:02:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ noescape has just published a now post : Innodis Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/noescape</link><description>Innodis Ltd, a public listed company founded in 1973, averages an annual turnover of almost MUR 4 billion. We are presently one of the largest groups involved in food and non-food production and distribution in Mauritius...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/noescape?08d1e9c2-223f-11ee-bf65-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Divgi-TTS was hacked. Due to the extreme low level of security, a huge amount of confident</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Divgi-TTS  Headquarters: 75 General Block Midc, Pune, Maharashtra, 411 026, India Phone Number: +91 2027302170 Website: www.divgi-tts.com Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/divgi-warner-private-limited</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?08d1ec58-223f-11ee-a1cb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Eastin Hotel Makkasan Bangkok was hacked. Customers' financial and personal information ha</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Eastin Hotel Makkasan Bangkok  Eastin Hotel Makkasan Bangkok is a company based out of Thailand.  Address: 1091/343 New Petchburi Road, Makkasan, Ratchathewi, Bangkok 10400, Thailand Phone: +66 2 651 7600 Website: https://www.eastinhotelsresidences.com/eastingrandsathornbangkok Twitter: https://twitter.com/EastinHotels Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/eastingrandsathorn Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/EastinGrandSathorn YouTube: https://youtu.be/e4JRglQefnw</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?08d1ee06-223f-11ee-b96e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : SMS-SME was hacked. A huge amount of confidential information was stolen, information of c</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is SMS-SME   SMS-SME was founded in 1993 by the top engineers from the Korean shipyard and global classification society. SMS-SME had a technology license partnership with Marco Neptune Germany at its launch. In 2002, we further innovated and established our own technology and design philosophy as an independent maker by ourselves. With an innovative product line and technology, SMS-SME has made rapid growth at Korean major shipyards who led the golden age of global shipbuilding. SMS-SME successfully expanded business worldwide, especially to the major shipyards in China and Japan to serve global ship owners and customers.   Headquarters: 75 Huntington St, Brooklyn, New York, 11231, United States Phone Number: (718) 875-6700 Website: www.sms-sme.com Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/sms-co-ltd-</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?08d1ef35-223f-11ee-917f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Algeiba.com has a critical level of security on its network. Customer and partner data is </title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Algeiba.com  Creating the best technology solutions to transform organizations around the globe has been our vision for more than 14 years. We started our journey standing out as the best infrastructure boutique in the Southern Cone. We incorporated new skills to create software of all kinds, as well as to get involved with business areas and secure them from any place and device with the mission of enabling our Clients to be successful.  Headquarters: 771 Paraná, Buenos Aires, Ciudad Autónoma de Buenos Aires, C1017AAO, Argentina Phone Number: +54 1139885519 Website: www.algeiba.com Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/algeiba-s-a- Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/algeibait Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/algeibasa</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?08d1f0da-223f-11ee-b169-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Amber Court 2020 was hacking. A lot of customers' personal information was stolen.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Amber Court 2020  Since 1968, under the loving care and guidance of Alfred and Judith Schonberger, they set the standard for quality care and lifestyle for seniors, in a residential setting. This holistic approach for an individual’s well-being, physically, mentally and emotionally, is at the heart of the Amber Court Family experience.  Headquarters: 1155 E Jersey St, Elizabeth, New Jersey, 07201, United States Phone Number: (908) 352-9200 Website: www.ambercourtal.com Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/ambercourtal</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?08d1f20e-223f-11ee-9623-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Maruchan Inc</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Maruchan ramen is a very popular brand of noodles in the United-States. The noodles are made in the United-States. Maruchan, one of the largest instant noodle brands internationally.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?08d1f342-223f-11ee-af12-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a now post : Schmidt Salzman &amp; Moran, Ltd</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira</link><description>With 35 years of practice in real estate taxation, Schmidt Salzman &amp; Moran, Ltd. aggressively pursues the lowest possible real estate taxes for its clients’ commercial, industrial and multi-unit residential properties. This company has not given us even the lowest price for their customers' personal information. If they don't need it, we are sure there are many of you who are interested.More that 70GB will be uploaded soon.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/akira?08d1f49d-223f-11ee-8fca-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Wright Moore DeHart Dupuis &amp; Hutchinson</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>For years, the accounting firm of Wright, Moore, DeHart, Dupuis &amp;amp; Hutchinson (WMDDH) has been providing quality, personalized financial guidance to individuals and businesses. WMDDH's expertise ranges from basic tax management and accounting services to more in-depth services such as audits, financial statements, litigation support, management advisory and consulting services. WMDDH has an extensive background dealing with the oil and gas industry, and we service clients ranging from small companies to multi-national operations. WMDDH takes the approach that we are your partner in business. By combining our expertise, experience and the team mentality of our staff, we assure that every client receives the close analysis and attention they deserve. Our dedication to high standards, hiring of seasoned professionals, and work ethic has provided that level of service for our clients across the country. We take pride in building long-term relationships with our clients and are committed to providing the highest level of personalized service in the industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?08d1f5de-223f-11ee-916e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 10:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ qilin has just published a now post : Better System Co.,Ltd</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin</link><description>Some of the data taken from the servers of this company can be found below</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin?08d1f73b-223f-11ee-972b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 10:07:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ noescape has just published a now post : Protactics</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/noescape</link><description>Protactics is a Colombian company that provides security and defense solutions for companies and governments in Latin America. We have data such as passports, ID cards/certificates/agreements/contracts/confidential docum...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/noescape?08d1f873-223f-11ee-8c44-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : CONSOLENERGY.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>Home - CONSOL Energy Inc.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1f9a5-223f-11ee-b615-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 18:02:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : KALEAERO.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?08d1fb34-223f-11ee-8e45-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 18:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>