<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><atom:link href="https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a new victim : Papel Prensa SA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</link><description>Papel Prensa SA is an Argentina-based company engaged in the manufacture of newsprint paper. Confidential contracts, agreements, personal employee information and other business docs. About 120GB. Please wait for the release.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 12:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ arvinclub has just published a new victim : Parsian Bitumen</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/arvinclub</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/arvinclub</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:07:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : varian.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>An American 3 billion dollar revenue Siemens Healthineers company! Varian Medical Systems, Inc. designs, manufactures, sells, and services medical devices and software products for treating cancer and other medical conditions worldwide. It operates t...</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/f639f12c6f811637663da5e1efab5b56.png" type="image/png" length="125202" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : IBL</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>total size of 161Gb.   Quick scope of data we have downloaded from your network:   payments  contracts  agreements  salaries  registration documents  financial data  quality control  medicine recipes  medicine tests  medicine preparation guides  IBL OPS data  United Brands data  IBL Logistics data  Searle pharma data </description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/c86928d0362368bbc8a8cb9049a4605e.png" type="image/png" length="56443" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : premierbpo.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Back Office Services  Customer Care Services  IT Services  Medical Billing  Software Support</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/b51553de0dc786133164ec487eb32d78.png" type="image/png" length="1319644" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a new victim : Delaney Browne Recruitment</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</link><description>Delaney Browne Appointments is a recruitment agency serving companies and candidates in Buckinghamshire and Berkshire. We are based in Reading. Since 1999 our dedicated team of fully qualified consultants and support staff have been specialising in temporary and permanent placements within the office sector, from director level to junior support and across a broad spectrum of industry sectorshttps://www.delaneybrowne.co.uk/</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/8713227178c72385fd52409c70b3db1f.png" type="image/png" length="100400" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a new victim : Oregon Sports Medicine</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</link><description>The goal of the skilled orthopedic team at Sports Medicine Oregon in Tigard and Wilsonville, Oregon, is to restore your active lifestyle. Serving all ages and levels of athletes, from the weekend warrior to the professional player, individuals receive the highest quality orthopedic care available. The practice has served the Northwest communities for more than 24 years, and Sports Medicine Oregon has been the go-to medical team for the Timbers even before they were a Major League Soccer team. The doctors take pride in providing comprehensive care at the offices, which feature on-site X-rays, outpatient physical therapy, and an adjoining surgery center. The practice specializes in sports injuries, including Achilles tendon injuries along with hip, knee, elbow, shoulder, foot, and hand injuries. Trust the practice with your ACL reconstruction, rotator cuff repair, or treatment for arthritis, hammertoe and foot fractures. Even if your injury isn’t directly related to sports, the team can help. The thorough, compassionate care provided by the specially-trained physicians is second to none. Make an appointment for a consultation today by calling and speaking with a friendly staff member or use the online tool to schedule.https://www.sportsmedicineoregon.com</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/cf7699d12e9bbc88cdcd8a77ab8a78b1.png" type="image/png" length="143516" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a new victim : SatCom Marketing</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</link><description>SatCom Marketing, LLC SatCom Marketing built its reputation as a leading teleservices provider to the cable/broadband industry. SatCom specializes in outbound sales, inbound sales, customer service calls, survey work and lead generation for business and consumer markets. We have deep experience in marketing and selling voice, video and data products. In addition, we have a wealth of experience in upselling ancillary products like internet speed upgrades, DVR service, digital tiers and premium channels. Our mission is to deliver quality sales and meaningful customer interactions for our clients to help them meet their business goals and ROI objectives. SatCom is a sales organization, focused on delivering quality sales and the highest close rates in the industry. We believe in a consultative sales approach which means tailoring our presentations to the needs of the customer. SatCom was founded with the idea that quality is the cornerstone of our business.http://www.satcommarketing.com/</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/0e9b2aeba3140d072bdb88522ed45e2e.png" type="image/png" length="128236" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Rayden Solicitors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Rayden Solicitors is an award-winning specialist firm of family law solicitors with offices in Beaconsfield, Berkhamsted, Birmingham, Bishop’s Stortford, Epping, Hampstead, Harpenden, London Bridge and St Albans. Our solicitors advise on all aspects of family law and are experts in financial and children matters relating to relationship breakdown, divorce and separation. Our clients are based across the UK and internationally.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/0b1d68648d1fdd524378f7a4cf0179c0.png" type="image/png" length="213321" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 15:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : haynesintl.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>haynesintl.comHaynes International, Inc., headquartered in Kokomo, Indiana, is one of the largest producers of corrosion-resistant and high-temperature alloys. In addition to Kokomo, Haynes has manufacturing facilities in Arcadia, Louisiana, and Mo...</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/44a0dc7a1be5afc4ad6d99085f150ff7.png" type="image/png" length="153536" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ everest has just published a new victim : Kovair Software Data Leak</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/everest</link><description>The set dates are out, so we post the entire archive Part1 https://dropmefiles.com/3GRYp Part2 https://dropmefiles.com/nAayA Part3 https://dropmefiles.com/tmhIh Part4 https://dropmefiles.com/K5zYz Part5 https://dropmefiles.com/6rp1U Part6 https://dropmefiles.com/5j6VM Password: &amp;amp;#B”a3Arcj}eOfoQ==Fh</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/e53d680d8acf307c7046612aa38bc090.png" type="image/png" length="95852" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/everest</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 08:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Henlaw</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Henderson, Franklin, Starnes &amp;amp; Holt, P.A. Founded in 1924, Henderson, Franklin, Starnes &amp;amp; Holt, P.A. is one of the largest and most experienced full-service law firms between Tampa and Miami. With over 55 attorneys who live, work and have deep roots in Southwest Florida, Henderson Franklin provides high-quality, personalized legal services to a roster of corporate and individual clients.  Founded on a culture of adhering to the highest ethical standards, integrity, and good citizenship, Henderson Franklin upholds these principles while remaining deeply invested in the Southwest Florida community. We act as trusted advisors and partners to our clients throughout every stage of their business.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/fce049862c5cb7f3a05496d631cda346.png" type="image/png" length="303905" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 07:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ arvinclub has just published a new victim : Draje food industrial group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/arvinclub</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/arvinclub</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 06:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : atser.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>In 1996, ATSER’s Team led in the development and deployment of a Material Acceptance Testing Systems (MATS). ATSER® pioneered the development of this type of software for the transportation industry and for its use in alternative delivery programs</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/9f652e98962350ddeb7eb2e0ca9c106f.png" type="image/png" length="240471" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:08:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : scottevest.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>SCOTTeVEST is a clothing company based in Ketchum, Idaho which specializes in garments with conduit systems and specialized pockets and compartments for holding mobile phones, tablet computers and other portable electronic devices.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/a7d69c7f9adf6d5a1dc9e0da6e3c9b0f.png" type="image/png" length="251579" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Galicia en Goles</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Galicia en Goles is a company that operates in the Media and Entertainment industry. It employs 1,001-2,000 people and has $500M-$1B of revenue</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/adcb27c25ae9aacc5fac1f730af6807d.png" type="image/png" length="1367977" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:02:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : iqcontrols.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>We specialize in designing, building and installing electrical control systems, PLC programming and HMI programming.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/8cffabbe2e7cb09fc6623b1d0b4f5f9c.png" type="image/png" length="256591" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : armortex.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>Armortex® has been manufacturing Bullet, Blast and Forced Entry Resistant products for more than thirty years. Our product line includes Armortex® brand fiberglass composite panels, glass, and containment glazing, fixed windows and transaction window...</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/888ae1a619a1f409e116ac9619d4c4a9.png" type="image/png" length="293233" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : mipe.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>Mission Petroleum Carriers, Inc is a bulk commodity transport company operating throughout Texas and surrounding states. Mission’s primary focus is the gathering and transportation of crude oil. Based in San Antonio, Texas, Mission has been providing...</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/4d118b9b3775cd7b2cb903f1459ec365.png" type="image/png" length="243052" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : tetco.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>TETCO, Inc. is a San Antonio-based company, owned and operated by the Tom E. Turner family for more than 60 years. Food service franchises, petrochemical distribution, and heavy truck and trailer repairs are the company’s primary revenue sources, wit...</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/3778fd1eac12b745f4e46e6467bb10e3.png" type="image/png" length="239103" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragroup has just published a new victim : P****X</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/ragroup</link><description /><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/c97f782c1fb6c9d5d1a6d6186a6c4930.png" type="image/png" length="79283" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/ragroup</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragroup has just published a new victim : Z****ta</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/ragroup</link><description /><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/d82810e7435f55d255267447d88cc7b4.png" type="image/png" length="86561" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/ragroup</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a new victim : Koury Engineering</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</link><description>Koury Engineering provides geotechnical engineering, material testing, and inspection services for residential and commercial construction projects throughout Southern California. More that 80GB of confidential contracts, agreements and NDAs, complete employeedata, projects information and much other documents will be uploaded later. All questions to messages section please.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:02:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : SBS Construction</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>SBS Construction, headquartered in Boerne, Texas has been in operation since 1995. Along with its regional office in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, SBS offers a full range of design-build, general contracting and construction management services to an elite group </description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/f6066361cba0ad4577a68bf849fcde52.png" type="image/png" length="614556" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Grupo Garza Ponce was hacked! Due to a massive company vulnerability, more than 2 TB of se</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Headquarters: 1000 Zaragoza 1, Monterrey, Nl, 64000, Mexico Phone Number: +52 8181503500 Website: www.grupogp.com.mx  Grupo Garza Ponce is a Mexican construction company based in Monterrey, Nuevo León. It was founded in 1966 by civil engineer José María Garza Ponce after he decided to take advantage of the boom in public works that Mexico was experiencing during that time. </description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/f026859d54a4b6ea88a7ce981dd9ebd5.png" type="image/png" length="1153702" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Pharmatech Repblica Dominicana was hacked. All sensitive company and customer information </title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Who is Pharmatech Repblica Dominicana  Leading company in the commercialization of pharmaceutical products in the Dominican Republic.  Website: www.pharmatechrd.com Revenue: $14.1M Santo Domingo: Calle Desiderio Valverde No.103, Zona Universitaria, Santo Domingo, D.N.,  Rep. Dom. Tel.: 809-620-8000 X 221; Fax: 809-682-1333 Santiago:  Ave. Juan Pablo Duarte,Plaza Las Barajas (1er Nivel) #103-104, Santiago, Rep. Dom. Tel.: 809-276-5286; Fax: 809-276-5289 Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/pharmatechdominicana Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/pharmatechrd</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/a4f152bc4be53e0269f85129aa423389.png" type="image/png" length="1839969" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ arvinclub has just published a new victim : seaside-kish co</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/arvinclub</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/arvinclub</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ nokoyawa has just published a new victim : Studio Domaine LLC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/nokoyawa</link><description>Studio Domaine is an innovative design firm dedicated to creating personalized interiors for residential and model homes. Our custom design services span broad styles and sensibilities providing our clients with their own &amp;quot;signature&amp;quot; style. What began in 1989 as Barbara&amp;#x27;s Interiors has now...</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/b96ec10fda84f2d64533c671b8b9114a.png" type="image/png" length="153478" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/nokoyawa</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ monti has just published a new victim : Abatti Companies - Press Release</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/monti</link><description>Abatti Companies is a vertically integrated group of companies that handles all facets of farm products from field to market. In 1981 Alex Abatti Jr. started as a custom harvest operator that later began farming to become one of the largest farmers in the Imperial Valley, California.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/ce2d8d9c82b42cee17811a7fee55bbe7.png" type="image/png" length="57333" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/monti</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Ofimedic</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Medical Software</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/9117a6b9a19fb84a62f4d71b3e81b80b.png" type="image/png" length="467858" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 06:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : THECHANGE</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>ESTABLISHED IN NOVEMBER, 1993 Now a driving force in the UK IT Distribution channel, The Change Organisation began its journey back in 1993.    Starting from humble beginnings (a garage in Kent), we have continued to achieve year on year organic growth through delivering not only the right products at the right price, but in providing maximum product availability, flexibility, excellent logistics &amp;amp; a genuinely personable customer service..  ‍ Almost 30 years on, the company has evolved into a well-oiled machine, operating across 4 sites with a group turnover of £80 million. Our 70+ staff all possess a shared passion for their personal and our collective corporate development.    As the commercial world moves inexorably towards e-commerce, AI, and automated telephony, the Change Organisation continues to uphold it’s maxim of providing traditional service in the modern manner.     We believe this demands dedicated and empowered account managers answering your calls. A culture of full accountability with a commitment to effect quick resolutions (when we’ve fallen short) establishing long term relationships built on trust.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/0c829ae2210f888c5df05810d9c0df23.png" type="image/png" length="316330" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 05:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a new victim : H********** ********* ***</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/bianlian</link><description>Software provider in healthcare industry.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/ea0c175c48ac883d14e8c55b41fe5658.png" type="image/png" length="44485" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/bianlian</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 22:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a new victim : Spokane Spinal Sports Care Clinic</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/bianlian</link><description>Spinal &amp;amp; Sports Care Clinic is a medical group practice located in Spokane Valley, WA that specializes in Massage Therapy and Chiropractic.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/36a49ec39882b1f91cab058d5e779518.png" type="image/png" length="182814" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/bianlian</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 22:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : pointpleasant.k12.nj.us</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>Point Pleasant Borough School District</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/2a5d013765994271a84c7cb48941e955.png" type="image/png" length="93180" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ nokoyawa has just published a new victim : Roman Catholic Diocese of Albany</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/nokoyawa</link><description>The Roman Catholic Diocese of Albany covers 14 counties in Eastern New York including the south west corner of a 15th county. Its Mother Church is the Cathedral of the Immaculate Conception in the city of Albany.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/d7e90b70c7f6ae776751c678d0a03c42.png" type="image/png" length="106544" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/nokoyawa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 15:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a new victim : Venture General Agency</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</link><description>Venture General Agency, LLC (VGA) is a family run Texas based Managing General Agency. These guys are not very talkative. All the data we have from this company will be released here next week. Personal docs and customer information, contracts and payments details - everything will be shared. If you are interested in something specific, let us know in messages section.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ akira has just published a new victim : Datawatch Systems</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</link><description>Datawatch Systems experts work in partnership with you to design,install, and operate a security system to safeguard your facility. It&amp;#x27;s frustrating when one tries to save someone&amp;#x27;s property andbecome a victim for himself. We took from these experts 100  GB of data containing confidential agreements and contracts, personal documents, customers data and their projects details. Watch your data! Uploading is coming.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/akira</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ rhysida has just published a new victim : United Tractors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/rhysida</link><description>United Tractors United Tractors is a heavy equipment distribution company headquartered in Jakarta, Indonesia.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/rhysida</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:07:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : admsc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>Al Doha Maintenance &amp;amp; Services Centre (ADMSC) was founded in the year 1997 by Mr. John. B. Carnelio with a vision of providing Quality Services to the fast-emerging Qatari Market.Since its establishment, ADMSC has developed a dynamic business app...</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/d447ffb8e922c6272c43b69a5af846cb.png" type="image/png" length="126920" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : riggsabney</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description> What makes us great. Founded in 1972 by four graduates from the University of Tulsa College of Law, Riggs Abney is one of Oklahoma’s largest law firms. Riggs, Abney, Neal &amp;amp; Turpen, merged with the firm Robinson, Lewis, Orbison, Smith and Coyle in 1994 to become Riggs, Abney, Neal, Turpen, Orbison &amp;amp; Lewis. Today, the firm is known simply as Riggs Abney, with offices in Tulsa, Oklahoma City and Colorado, providing broad based legal counsel and representation in all aspects of law.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/c640b27870b39a3df25e429fe38e34e1.png" type="image/png" length="229596" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a new victim : RevZero, Inc</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</link><description>We focus on medical device contract manufacturing, 5-axis milling &amp;amp; medical device machining as per the client’s needs and requirements. Visit our website now! RevZero, Inc. is an Agile Medical Device Manufucatring company. Capabilities include Swiss screw, wire EDM, EDM hole drilling, CNCl milling and turning, and cleaning and citric passivation for rapid prototyping and volume manufacturing requirementshttps://www.revzeroinc.com/</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/311fd51645ac92b6ea00454c2fdfcc22.png" type="image/png" length="98772" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 8base has just published a new victim : Rossman Realty Group, inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</link><description>See all the Southwest FL Homes and Condos for Sale or Rent - up to 72 hours before they appear on Zillow! We also offer property management services! Rossman Realty Group, Inc has a large inventory of Fannie Mae listings and the expertise to help you acquire one! Whether you are searching for your first home, your dream or vacation home, REO or foreclosure, investment property, commercial property, full time annual or seasonal vacation rentals, Gulf Access homes or vacant lots, you have found the right place!https://www.rossmanrentals.com/https://www.rossmanhomes.com/</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/4a1d44339727864642eb16862c938a24.png" type="image/png" length="107870" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/8base</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Tempur Sealy International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>Tempur Sealy International, Inc. is an American manufacturer of mattresses and bedding products. It was formed when Tempur-Pedic International, a manufacturer of memory foam mattresses acquired its biggest competitor Sealy Corporation in 2012.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/f5a10cd663359f051dd5acae14cd1068.png" type="image/png" length="269064" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : bestmotel.de</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>Best Motel offers everything for a convenient stay in Vilsbiburg, Landshut (less than 20 car minutes away) and surroundings.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/d35b48a8f1ce93d790fbd92111561667.png" type="image/png" length="121176" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : fec-corp.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>Federal Electric Corp., Ltd., FEC, established in 1978, is an exclusive sole manufacturer of electric home appliances under the well - known SHARP brand in Thailand.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/6528547f3eb486b865d85931234fc3bf.png" type="image/png" length="97563" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a new victim : constructioncrd.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</link><description>!! some confidential info from servers this company. !!Pour les experts en construction résidentielle dans la grande région de Québec, comptez sur Construction CRD</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/e50e877263e0a1e294b02a2441a0597b.png" type="image/png" length="109335" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/lockbit3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a new victim : Helen F. Dalton Lawyers</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</link><description>With over 25 years experience specializing in Personal Injury and Labor Law, the Law Offices of Helen F. Dalton and Associates has the experience and resources necessary to fight for you.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/0595d8c53b21999b9fbcf26bcc5fcc3d.png" type="image/png" length="660370" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/alphv</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ monti has just published a new victim : Bickel &amp; Brewer - Press Release</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/monti</link><description>Founded in 1984, Bickel &amp;amp; Brewer has earned a reputation as one of the most successful law firms in the United States practicing exclusively in the field of complex commercial litigation and dispute resolution.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/d1636c2369c4e8652f96a8c777681db7.png" type="image/png" length="861093" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/monti</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 15:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a new victim : SHERMAN.EDU</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/clop</link><description>Chiropractic School - Sherman College of Chiropractic - Spartanburg, SC</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/df04b6c9bb929424799f990bed81fbae.png" type="image/png" length="36217" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/clop</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ karakurt has just published a new victim : COSI</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/karakurt</link><description>COSI, Columbus, Ohio&amp;#x27;s dynamic Center of Science and Industry, inspires the scientists, dreamers, and innovators of tomorrow. We&amp;#x27;ve taken about 75GBs of data from this organization. You will find there their projects information, lots of accounting and financial documents, contracts (some of them are confidential), clients contacts, donations information an so on. There are also databases containing clients, partners and employee data, transactions and correspondence. Wait for the release.</description><enclosure url="https://images.ransomware.live/screenshots/posts/53e44a522d50181a073c89fc63b2bc17.png" type="image/png" length="114770" /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/group/karakurt</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>